<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>by Jim Fitzsimmons</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 09:49:54 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 09:49:54 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cloudflare</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I just switched my nameservers over to clouldflare and with a bit of tweaking, I now have a secure https:// site instead of an unsecure site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know that it matters much as there’s only text on the site for the most part, and a few links but hey what the heck - it was &lt;em&gt;*free&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think there’s a chance that having a secure site will give your SEO a bump too so time will tell if this tweak was worth the effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Give us five minutes and we’ll supercharge your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cloudflare.com/&quot;&gt;CloudFlare - The web performance &amp;amp; security company&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 23:23:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/13/CloudFlare-The-web-performance-security-company/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/13/CloudFlare-The-web-performance-security-company/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>iOS - iOS 10 - Apple</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today is the day for Apple’s latest OS&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Everything you love is now even better with iOS 10, our biggest release yet. Express yourself in bold new ways in Messages. Find your route with beautifully redesigned Maps. Relive memories like never before in Photos. And use the power of Siri in more apps than ever. There’s so much to say about iOS 10&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.apple.com/ios/ios-10/&quot;&gt;iOS - iOS 10 - Apple&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 11:54:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/13/iOS-iOS-10-Apple/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/13/iOS-iOS-10-Apple/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>System Folder</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I miss the older Macs at times and System Folder is a lot of fun&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In this weblog I talk about my personal experience with vintage Macs and what I still do with my machines. I also try to collect useful information about classic hardware and software, republishing old articles and tips, mainly taken from 10-15 year-old magazines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://systemfolder.wordpress.com/weblog/&quot;&gt;System Folder&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 10:29:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/12/System-Folder/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/12/System-Folder/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Best Unlimited Online Backup and Cloud Storage Services</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you care about the stuff on your Mac, you need to back up. This service has saved my bacon more than once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Backblaze cloud backup has backed up over 200 million GB of data for Mac and PC laptops and desktops. To date Backblaze has restored over 10 billion files for our customers. Without our cloud backup service, those files would have been lost forever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.backblaze.com/&quot;&gt;The Best Unlimited Online Backup and Cloud Storage Services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:47:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/12/The-Best-Unlimited-Online-Backup-and-Cloud-Storage-Services/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/12/The-Best-Unlimited-Online-Backup-and-Cloud-Storage-Services/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PeakHour 3, beautiful network monitoring and reporting for your Mac</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This looks interesting if you need to keep track of a network on a Mac
&amp;gt; Monitor your Internet, WiFi and network performance, right from your menu bar.
&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://peakhourapp.com/&quot;&gt;PeakHour 3, beautiful network monitoring and reporting for your Mac&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 21:26:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/10/PeakHour-3-beautiful-network-monitoring-and-reporting-for-your-Mac/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/10/PeakHour-3-beautiful-network-monitoring-and-reporting-for-your-Mac/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Macintosh Clone Era | Low End Mac</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Maybe a Macintosh Clone wasn’t such a good idea after all…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The first thing that happened was clone makers developing Mac OS computers that ran faster than Apple’s computers while costing less – the 110 MHz Radius System 100 in March 1995 when Apple’s fastest was the 100 MHz Power Mac 8100, the 120 MHz Power Computing Power 120 a month later, the 150 MHz PowerWave in October 1995, the quad 132 MHz Daystar Genesis MP 528 (the first multiprocessor Mac) in October 1995 and quad 150 MHz MP 600 in February 1996, the 200 MHz Power Tower in April 1996, the 250 MHz Umax SuperMac S900 with a second CPU slot in August 1996, and so on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://lowendmac.com/2016/the-macintosh-clone-era/&quot;&gt;The Macintosh Clone Era&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 21:21:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/10/The-Macintosh-Clone-Era-Low-End-Mac/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/10/The-Macintosh-Clone-Era-Low-End-Mac/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where to Buy Ram - Ramjet</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.macmemory.com/pages/about-ramjet&quot;&gt;Ramjet.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;As fellow Mac enthusiasts, we noticed a dearth of reliable upgrade products that meet or exceed Apple’s standards of quality and service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;That’s why in 1996, we launched Ramjet, a family-run company out of Champaign, Illinois, dedicated to helping do-it-yourself Mac lovers like us get the most performance and life out of their Macs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/08/2016-09-08-where-to-buy-ram-ramjet/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/08/2016-09-08-where-to-buy-ram-ramjet/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where to Buy Ram - Data Memory Systems</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.datamemorysystems.com/&quot;&gt;Data Memory Systems &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;DMS has been supplying the electronics industry with high quality components since 1963 and memory modules since 1987. We are one of the first original Memory Companies to support Apple Computer and have been doing so for over 20 years. We also support a vast array of Computer Memory for PC’s and Servers. Data Memory Systems is a New Hampshire based Corporation located in Tax Free Salem NH. Our philosophy is to supply the customer with the best quality memory at the best possible price. We pride ourselves on exceptional service with the most knowledgeable and courteous sales staff in the business, with many years of experience. At DMS there is no voice message prompts, WE ANSWER THE PHONES! We welcome call-in orders or questions or you can just order on-line (SAME LOW PRICE!). Here at DMS we run our own in-house test lab. We can assure you that your memory will be DMS Certified tested Memory. All our Memory is tested in the most current state-of-the-art systems. This is done to put your mind at ease for years of trouble-free operation. In the unlikely event you do receive a defective Memory module, DMS will replace it free of charge, before we even receive the defective memory back. DMS covers the cost of shipping to you as well as the return freight charges. DMS is the first Company to offer this service, with great customer satisfaction for over 20 years. Not all memory is the same. The lowest price is not always the best option. Once you’ve purchased DMS Certified Memory you will insist on it again for all your computer needs. We back that up with our LIFETIME GUARANTEE.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/08/2016-09-08-where-to-buy-ram-data-memory-systems/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/08/2016-09-08-where-to-buy-ram-data-memory-systems/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where to Buy Memory -Trans Intl</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.transintl.com/&quot;&gt;Home page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;HOME/ ABOUT US
Founded in 1988 Trans International is known for Maximizing Macs &amp;amp; PCs. Being an Apple Hardware developer for years, specializing in MemoryUpgrades and Quality Storage Solutions first to the users in the market,Consistently breaking limitation barriers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Trans International has always maintained a strong reputation among leading manufacturers, resellers ,retailers and power users for designing, developing, producing and supporting products that anticipates the current and future needs of the ever changing computer Industry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Maximizing Macs with tested quality Memory and Storage Solutions with Matchless Service and Support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/08/2016-09-08-where-to-buy-memory-trans-intl/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/08/2016-09-08-where-to-buy-memory-trans-intl/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where to Buy RAM - Other World Computing</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;My Upgrades
The simple, 3-step process that takes the guesswork out of finding upgrades and accessories compatible with your Mac.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://eshop.macsales.com/MyOWC/&quot;&gt;MyOWC at MacSales.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 13:40:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/07/MyOWC-at-MacSales-com/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/07/MyOWC-at-MacSales-com/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
