<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>by Jim Fitzsimmons</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 13:59:04 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 13:59:04 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Caret is a  Premium Markdown Editor for Mac - Windows - Linux</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Caret is a markdown editor for Windows, Mac and Linux that looks kind of neat. It’s got a lot of features. Your best bet is to hit the link below and watch the movie of all Caret can do&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://caret.io/&quot;&gt;Caret - Premium Markdown Editor for Mac / Windows / Linux&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 11:17:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/18/Caret-Premium-Markdown-Editor-for-Mac-Windows-Linux/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/18/Caret-Premium-Markdown-Editor-for-Mac-Windows-Linux/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Cloud CMS for Jekyll</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This looks pretty neat if you want to quickly blog with jekyll and want a wysisyg editor simiar to wordpress. I’ve tried it, but I think I like my current workflow better though&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The best of both worlds
Developers and non-developers easily collaborate on sites without stepping on each other’s toes.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Developers have complete control over the source code and simply build static or Jekyll websites.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Non-developers update content visually using the CloudCannon inline editor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cloudcannon.com/&quot;&gt;The Cloud CMS for Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 00:06:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/18/The-Cloud-CMS-for-Jekyll-CloudCannon/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/18/The-Cloud-CMS-for-Jekyll-CloudCannon/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cloudcannon</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;this looks &lt;strong&gt;really&lt;/strong&gt; neat: a &lt;a href=&quot;http://cloudcannon.com&quot;&gt;CMS for Jekyll.&lt;/a&gt; If you want a free site to host your pages, create one on &lt;a href=&quot;pages.githbub.com&quot;&gt;github pages&lt;/a&gt; and then when you hit published the content gets build and pushed to your github pages site easily&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The best of both worlds
&lt;br /&gt;Developers and non-developers easily collaborate on sites without stepping on each other’s toes.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Developers have complete control over the source code and simply build static or Jekyll websites.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Non-developers update content visually using the CloudCannon inline editor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/17/cloudcannon/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/17/cloudcannon/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ad Blocker Not Required</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I have made some &lt;strong&gt;pretty significant&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;changes&lt;/strong&gt; in recent times to this site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in &lt;a href=&quot;https://ramseeker.com/2016/04/19/switched-to-jekyll-from-wordpress/&quot;&gt;April&lt;/a&gt;, I moved &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pagely.com&quot;&gt;from expensive wordpress hosting&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href=&quot;pages.github.com&quot;&gt;free hosting&lt;/a&gt; for this site and moved from using the much bloated wordpresss to &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;something a lot simpler&lt;/a&gt; for my writing and blogging needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then just this past week I went a bit further and figured out how to make this site secure with https://ramseeker.com instead of just using http://ramseeker.com. I don’t know why you would really need to have this site secure, as I’m not accepting credit cards or any sensitive data, but Google is giving secure sites a bit of an edge in the search results, and when it comes to SEO every little bit counts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my effort continue optimizing the site to the bare minimum required, I thought what the heck, I might as well &lt;strong&gt;disable all the trackers&lt;/strong&gt; too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-results&quot;&gt;The Results&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Screenshot%20from%202016-09-16%2009-01-54.png&quot; alt=&quot;now this is fast&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This site now loads &lt;strong&gt;in about half a second&lt;/strong&gt;, and has a pagespeed score of 100%. It’s kind of hard to beat 100 percent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compare this to a very popular tech blog:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Screenshot%20from%202016-09-16%2010-50-56.png&quot; alt=&quot;much slower website&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a heavy design and ad trackers galore, this site takes &lt;strong&gt;almost ten seconds to load&lt;/strong&gt;! Who has time to wait ten seconds?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ads-are-out-of-control&quot;&gt;Ads Are Out of Control&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m old enough to remember a pre-Google internet and pre-adsense and ad-tracker web, and I have to tell you - it was glorious. Maybe because we were paying much more for our internet access, or our computers were much slower and didn’t display in as many colors and resolution and perhaps I’m remembering though rose colored glasses, but it seems to me the current web has become one bloated mess. I don’t need to have ads pushed down my throat all the time just to get to the content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know that ads on the web are inevitable, and hosting costs money and time is valuable and publishers need to be paid, but some have gotten awful greedy and have over-filled their sites with more and more ads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;say-goodbye-to-ad-trackers&quot;&gt;Say GoodBye to Ad Trackers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve tried to use adsense a few times here in the past and risk/reward was always not worth it and I found all they did was display non-relevant ads half the time and they cluttered up the design. Add ‘ad blindness’ into the mix and for me it was an very easy decision to kick them to the curb.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve read some other sites recently that have disabled trackers and analytics and I thought, heck I &lt;strong&gt;might as well do the same&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It took some time for me to get the courage to do this. Checking your stats more than once a day becomes a bad habit and I’m the first to admit it’s fun to see your real-time stats or how many visitors a day you get or even how popular your ads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what do I do with that data? &lt;strong&gt;I have no idea&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only reason you really need analytics and stats is when you’re trying to sell ads or trying to sell the site. Seeing how the chances of either of those happening are mighty slim anyway I won’t miss the analytics or ads. This isn’t to say you won’t see ads on the site, because I like to make a few bucks for my efforts too, but ads will either be relatively non-intrusive or simple text links. Both load fast and like any other ad, can be ignored.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-cookies&quot;&gt;What Cookies?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Screenshot%20from%202016-09-16%2018-06-38.png&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My cookie policy? I don’t have one because I &lt;strong&gt;don’t collect any cookies whatsoever&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think I can get this site any more secure or simpler and easy to read, and &lt;strong&gt;I could care less about your viewing habits&lt;/strong&gt;. You can be sure I will have no idea that you visited by using a tracker. I don’t set cookies or track you in any way.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/16/ad-blocker-not-required/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/16/ad-blocker-not-required/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cloudflare</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I just switched my nameservers over to clouldflare and with a bit of tweaking, I now have a secure https:// site instead of an unsecure site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know that it matters much as there’s only text on the site for the most part, and a few links but hey what the heck - it was &lt;em&gt;*free&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think there’s a chance that having a secure site will give your SEO a bump too so time will tell if this tweak was worth the effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Give us five minutes and we’ll supercharge your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cloudflare.com/&quot;&gt;CloudFlare - The web performance &amp;amp; security company&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 23:23:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/13/CloudFlare-The-web-performance-security-company/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/13/CloudFlare-The-web-performance-security-company/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>iOS - iOS 10 - Apple</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today is the day for Apple’s latest OS&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Everything you love is now even better with iOS 10, our biggest release yet. Express yourself in bold new ways in Messages. Find your route with beautifully redesigned Maps. Relive memories like never before in Photos. And use the power of Siri in more apps than ever. There’s so much to say about iOS 10&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.apple.com/ios/ios-10/&quot;&gt;iOS - iOS 10 - Apple&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 11:54:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/13/iOS-iOS-10-Apple/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/13/iOS-iOS-10-Apple/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>System Folder</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I miss the older Macs at times and System Folder is a lot of fun&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In this weblog I talk about my personal experience with vintage Macs and what I still do with my machines. I also try to collect useful information about classic hardware and software, republishing old articles and tips, mainly taken from 10-15 year-old magazines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://systemfolder.wordpress.com/weblog/&quot;&gt;System Folder&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 10:29:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/12/System-Folder/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/12/System-Folder/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Best Unlimited Online Backup and Cloud Storage Services</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you care about the stuff on your Mac, you need to back up. This service has saved my bacon more than once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Backblaze cloud backup has backed up over 200 million GB of data for Mac and PC laptops and desktops. To date Backblaze has restored over 10 billion files for our customers. Without our cloud backup service, those files would have been lost forever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.backblaze.com/&quot;&gt;The Best Unlimited Online Backup and Cloud Storage Services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:47:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/12/The-Best-Unlimited-Online-Backup-and-Cloud-Storage-Services/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/12/The-Best-Unlimited-Online-Backup-and-Cloud-Storage-Services/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PeakHour 3, beautiful network monitoring and reporting for your Mac</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This looks interesting if you need to keep track of a network on a Mac
&amp;gt; Monitor your Internet, WiFi and network performance, right from your menu bar.
&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://peakhourapp.com/&quot;&gt;PeakHour 3, beautiful network monitoring and reporting for your Mac&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 21:26:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/10/PeakHour-3-beautiful-network-monitoring-and-reporting-for-your-Mac/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/10/PeakHour-3-beautiful-network-monitoring-and-reporting-for-your-Mac/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Macintosh Clone Era | Low End Mac</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Maybe a Macintosh Clone wasn’t such a good idea after all…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The first thing that happened was clone makers developing Mac OS computers that ran faster than Apple’s computers while costing less – the 110 MHz Radius System 100 in March 1995 when Apple’s fastest was the 100 MHz Power Mac 8100, the 120 MHz Power Computing Power 120 a month later, the 150 MHz PowerWave in October 1995, the quad 132 MHz Daystar Genesis MP 528 (the first multiprocessor Mac) in October 1995 and quad 150 MHz MP 600 in February 1996, the 200 MHz Power Tower in April 1996, the 250 MHz Umax SuperMac S900 with a second CPU slot in August 1996, and so on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://lowendmac.com/2016/the-macintosh-clone-era/&quot;&gt;The Macintosh Clone Era&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 21:21:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/09/10/The-Macintosh-Clone-Era-Low-End-Mac/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/09/10/The-Macintosh-Clone-Era-Low-End-Mac/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
